[A Mission of the Heart]
[مهمة القلب]
[Episode 20]
[الحلقة 20]
Thirteen years ago,
منذ ثلاثة عشر عامًا،
Ling Yuanhang's entire family was executed
تم إعدام عائلة لينغ يوانهانغ بأكملها
due to rebelling
بسبب التمرد
and embezzling military funds.
واختلاس الأموال العسكرية.
His eldest daughter, Ling Zhang, was sold to Yanyu Brothel.
تم بيع ابنته الكبرى، لينغ تشانغ، إلى بيت دعارة يانيو.
The whereabouts of his son, Ling Xiao, was unknown.
ولم يعرف بعد مكان تواجد ابنه لينغ شياو .
At 10, Ling Xiao had exceptional lightness skills
في سن العاشرة، كان لينغ شياو يتمتع بمهارات خفة استثنائية
and excelled in medicine.
وتفوق في الطب.
The ghost-masked man also knows about the Moon Stone.
الرجل ذو القناع الشبح يعرف أيضًا عن حجر القمر.
Back when the Ling family was purged,
عندما تم تطهير عائلة لينغ،
were there any survivors?
هل كان هناك أي ناجين؟
Zhao.
تشاو.
What are you thinking about?
ماذا تفكر فيه؟
Nothing.
لا شئ.
Did the Mu family have any survivors?
هل كان لعائلة مو أي ناجين؟
No.
لا.
My Lord.
سيدي.
Where is Commander Li?
أين القائد لي؟
Commander Li went to take a bath.
ذهب القائد لي للاستحمام.
Where would Zhao Yutang go to keep the appointment?
أين سيذهب تشاو يوتانغ للحفاظ على الموعد؟
Could it be Changsheng Temple?
هل يمكن أن يكون معبد تشانغشنغ؟
Shen Pan!
شين بان!
Has Yu come to you?
هل جاء يو إليك؟
No.
لا.
Crap!
هراء!
Yu is missing!
يو مفقود!
Yu is missing?
هل يو مفقود؟
Wasn't she with you?
ألم تكن معك؟
I think she was taken by Li Zhaoxia.
أعتقد أنها أخذت من قبل لي تشاو شيا.
Li Zhaoxia?
لي تشاوشيا؟
Why would he take Yu?
لماذا يأخذ يو؟
I found out that Li Zhaoxia
لقد اكتشفت أن لي تشاو شيا
might be the ghost-masked man.
ربما يكون الرجل المقنع الشبح.
Yu was probably taken
ربما تم أخذ يو
because of that.
بسبب ذلك.
You're saying Li Zhaoxia is the ghost-masked man?
هل تقول أن لي تشاو شيا هو الرجل المقنع الشبح؟
We must rescue Yu quickly.
يجب علينا إنقاذ يو بسرعة.
My Lord,
سيدي
we've tracked down the ghost-masked man's whereabouts.
لقد تعقبنا مكان تواجد الرجل المقنع الشبح.
Go!
يذهب!
Call the Imperial Guards!
اتصل بالحرس الإمبراطوري!
Commander Li,
القائد لي،
I have no grudge against you.
ليس لدي أي ضغينة ضدك.
Why are you doing this to me?
لماذا تفعل بي هذا؟
Why?
لماذا؟
Because you deserve to die!
لأنك تستحق الموت!
Youlan, whom you tortured to death,
يولان الذي عذبته حتى الموت،
was my sister, Ling Zhang.
كانت أختي، لينغ تشانغ.
I am Ling Xiao, the son of Ling Yuanhang,
أنا لينغ شياو، ابن لينغ يوانهانغ،
Vice Minister of the Judicial Review Court.
نائب وزير محكمة المراجعة القضائية.
It was Chen Zhao and Jiang Ning
كان تشن تشاو وجيانغ نينغ
who framed the Ling family!
من قام بتأطير عائلة لينغ!
It has nothing to do with me!
لا علاقة لي بذلك!
You're still making excuses!
مازلت تقدم الأعذار!
Do you really think
هل تعتقد حقا
I came here alone?
لقد جئت هنا وحدي؟
To tell you the truth,
لأقول لك الحقيقة،
if anything happens to me today,
إذا حدث لي أي شيء اليوم،
you won't survive either.
ولن تنجو أيضًا.
So what?
وماذا في ذلك؟
Get up!
استيقظ!
What you owe the Ling family—
ما تدين به لعائلة لينغ—
I'll make you pay for it
سأجعلك تدفع ثمنها
cut by cut.
قطع بقطع.
Ling Xiao!
لينغ شياو!
Stop.
قف.
You know everything?
هل تعرف كل شئ؟
Yes.
نعم.
You're going to stop me too?
هل ستوقفني أيضًا؟
Have you forgotten
هل نسيت؟
how our families were wiped out?
كيف تم القضاء على عائلاتنا؟
I haven't forgotten!
لم أنسى!
But Zhao Yutang shouldn't die here.
لكن تشاو يوتانغ لم يكن ينبغي أن يموت هنا.
We should expose his crimes
ينبغي علينا أن نكشف جرائمه
and clear our names openly and justly!
وتبرئة أسمائنا علانية وبحق!
Openly and justly?
بصراحة وعدل؟
Ningzhao.
نينغ تشاو.
You're still too naive.
مازلت ساذجًا جدًا.
The court today is corrupt.
المحكمة اليوم فاسدة.
There's no justice.
لا يوجد عدالة
There's no justice!
لا يوجد عدالة!
Zhao!
تشاو!
My Lord!
سيدي!
Shut up.
اسكت.
Fine.
بخير.
I won't go over there.
لن أذهب إلى هناك.
Zhao,
تشاو،
I have obtained
لقد حصلت على
all the evidence needed to bring Zhao Yutang to justice!
كل الأدلة اللازمة لتقديم تشاو يوتانغ للعدالة!
Release them first!
أطلق سراحهم أولاً!
Enough!
كافٍ!
Zhao,
تشاو،
Mrs. Chen's booklet
كتيب السيدة تشين
records all the evidence of Zhao Yutang's crimes!
تسجيل كافة الأدلة على جرائم تشاو يوتانغ!
The donations to Changsheng Temple
التبرعات لمعبد تشانغشنغ
were all embezzled by him!
لقد اختلسوا كل أموالهم!
With this,
مع هذا،
it's enough to clear the names of the Ling family and the Mu family!
يكفي تبرئة اسمي عائلة لينغ وعائلة مو!
Clear our names?
مسح أسمائنا؟
He caused the extermination of the Ling family.
كان سببًا في إبادة عائلة لينغ.
He caused my sister to die tragically in a brothel.
لقد تسبب في وفاة أختي بشكل مأساوي في بيت دعارة.
If I don't tear him into pieces,
إذا لم أمزقه إلى قطع،
it won't be enough to ease the hatred in my heart!
لن يكون كافيا لتخفيف الكراهية في قلبي!
Ling Xiao.
لينغ شياو.
Listen to me.
استمع لي.
I believe your father and mother
أنا أؤمن بأبيك وأمك
wouldn't want you to do this.
لا أريدك أن تفعل هذا.
All these years,
كل هذه السنوات،
your sister never looked for you
أختك لم تبحث عنك أبدًا
just because she wanted you to live well!
فقط لأنها أرادت لك أن تعيش حياة جيدة!
Thirteen years ago,
منذ ثلاثة عشر عامًا،
Ling Xiao was already dead.
لقد كان لينغ شياو ميتًا بالفعل.
Already dead!
لقد مات بالفعل!
Zhao!
تشاو!
Back when the Ling family was wiped out,
عندما تم القضاء على عائلة لينغ،
my master secretly took me to a valley.
لقد أخذني سيدي إلى الوادي سراً.
He told me
لقد قال لي
not to seek revenge.
عدم السعي للانتقام.
But when I found out my sister
ولكن عندما اكتشفت أختي
died an unnatural death
مات موتًا غير طبيعي
and was forced into a ghost marriage,
وأُجبرت على الزواج من شبح،
how could I not hate?
كيف لا أكره؟
So...
لذا...
that's why you were willing to help Xue Jingshu?
ولهذا السبب كنت على استعداد لمساعدة Xue Jingshu؟
Yes.
نعم.
I targeted everyone involved in ghost marriages!
لقد استهدفت كل من شارك في زواج الأشباح!
If I had known earlier
لو كنت أعرف في وقت سابق
that Zhao Yutang was the one who killed my sister,
أن تشاو يوتانغ هو الذي قتل أختي،
how could I have let him live until now?
كيف أتركه يعيش حتى الآن؟
What about Chen Zhao?
ماذا عن تشين تشاو؟
Why did you use Zhou Yue
لماذا استخدمت تشو يوي؟
to kill Chen Zhao?
لقتل تشين تشاو؟
Chen Zhao was my sister's fiancé.
كان تشين تشاو خطيب أختي.
But he colluded with Jiang Ning,
ولكنه تواطأ مع جيانغ نينغ،
intentionally framing my father
تعمد توريط والدي
and causing my sister
وتسبب في أختي
to end up in a brothel.
لينتهي به الأمر في بيت دعارة.
If I hadn't wanted to keep my identity secret,
لو لم أكن أرغب في إبقاء هويتي سرية،
I would have killed him with my own hands long ago.
لقد قتلته بيدي منذ زمن طويل.
Even so,
ومع ذلك،
your enemy is Zhao Yutang!
عدوك هو تشاو يوتانغ!
Why did you capture Yu?
لماذا قمت بإلقاء القبض على يو؟
No one can stop me.
لا أحد يستطيع ايقافي.
After I kill Zhao Yutang,
بعد أن قتلت تشاو يوتانغ،
I will apologize to you all.
سأعتذر لكم جميعا.
That's just your wishful thinking.
هذا مجرد تفكيرك المتمني.
Perhaps you all don't know yet,
ربما أنتم جميعا لا تعرفون ذلك بعد،
but my men will be here soon.
لكن رجالي سيكونون هنا قريبا.
No one can leave!
لا أحد يستطيع المغادرة!
Your men have been wiped out by us.
لقد تم القضاء على رجالك من قبلنا.
Impossible.
مستحيل.
Since that's the case,
وبما أن هذه هي الحالة،
let's all die here!
دعونا نموت جميعا هنا!
Crap!
هراء!
Zhao Yutang, I'm going to kill you!
تشاو يوتانغ، سأقتلك!
Zhao Yutang and the others framed loyal officials,
تشاو يوتانغ والآخرون قاموا بتوريط المسؤولين الموالين،
embezzled official silver,
اختلس الفضة الرسمية،
accepted bribes,
الرشاوى المقبولة،
sold official positions,
بيع المناصب الرسمية،
and corrupted the court's discipline.
وأفسد انضباط المحكمة.
In the end, they were beheaded.
وفي النهاية تم قطع رؤوسهم.
The names of the Ling and Mu families
أسماء عائلتي لينغ ومو
were cleared.
تمت التطهير.
I never intended to harm Yu.
لم أقصد أبدًا أن أؤذي يو.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Please help me...
من فضلك ساعدني...
apologize to Yu.
أعتذر إلى يو.
She has never blamed you.
إنها لم تلومك أبدًا.
Why did you save me?
لماذا انقذتني؟
Because you, Li Zhaoxia,
بسببك، لي تشاوشيا
are my subordinate.
هم مرؤوسي.
Why didn't you tell me from the start?
لماذا لم تخبرني منذ البداية؟
If I had told you earlier,
لو قلت لك في وقت سابق،
perhaps the outcome would have been different.
وربما كانت النتيجة مختلفة.
[Ministry of Punishments]
[وزارة العقوبات]
My Lord.
سيدي.
♪ The trace engraved upon my heart ♪
♪ الأثر المنقوش على قلبي ♪
♪ Grows clearer each time I dream ♪
♪ يصبح الأمر أكثر وضوحًا في كل مرة أحلم فيها ♪
Yu.
يو.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
♪ So familiar ♪
♪ مألوفة جدا ♪
♪ Yet forever out of reach ♪
♪ ومع ذلك فهي بعيدة عن متناول اليد إلى الأبد ♪
♪ Beautiful as a mirage ♪
♪ جميلة كالسراب ♪
My Lord, aren't we going to follow them?
يا سيدي، ألا نتبعهم؟
♪ My thoughts are soaked through with ink ♪
♪ أفكاري غارقة بالحبر ♪
What for?
لماذا؟
♪ Yet I don't know where to start ♪
♪ ولكنني لا أعرف من أين أبدأ ♪
So Lu Zhan can annoy me?
فهل يستطيع لو تشان أن يزعجني؟
♪ If hearts could draw each other near, no distance could stand between ♪
♪ لو استطاعت القلوب أن تقترب من بعضها البعض، فلن تقف أي مسافة بينها ♪
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
♪ You are the one thing I'm sure of ♪
♪ أنت الشيء الوحيد الذي أنا متأكد منه ♪